Guide to the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, Local 6 Records WAG.148
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Files
  - Series IV: Hotels
    - Great Northern: Minutes, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Greystone, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Hampshire House, 1948-1952 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Hampshire House: Minutes, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Harvard Club, 1953-1955 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Henry Hudson, 1945-1959 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Henry Hudson: Minutes, 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Hotel Association, 1958-1961 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Hotel Trades Council, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Justine Caterers, 1948, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Manhattan, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Manhattan: Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Martinique, 1950-1959 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Martinique: Minutes, 1955; 1959 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - McAlpin (Sheraton McAlpin/Sheraton Atlantic), 1942; 1948-1960 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - McAlpin (Sheraton McAlpin/Sheraton Atlantic): Minutes, 1951-1958 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - McCarthy, James, 1946-1953 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - New York Athletic Club, 1947-1954 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - New Yorker, 1948-1961 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - New Yorker: Minutes, 1951-1960 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Olcott, 1948-1959 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - One Fifth Avenue, 1948-1957 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Paramount, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Park Lane, 1948-1960 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Park Lane: Minutes, 1947-1959 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Park Royal, 1949-1958 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Park Royal: Minutes, 1955-1958 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Park Sheraton, 1948-1957 (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Park Sheraton: Minutes, 1948-1958 (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Piccadilly, 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Pierre, 1942; 1947-1960 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Minutes: Pierre, 1949-1960 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Plaza, 1950-1958 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Plaza: Minutes, 1947-1960 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Ritz Carlton, 1948-1951 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Ritz Carlton: Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Roosevelt, 1946-1961 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Roosevelt: Minutes, 1949-1960 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Saint George, 1947-1960 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Saint George: Minutes, 1949-1960 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Saint Moritz, 1948; 1955; 1961 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Saint Moritz: Minutes, 1954-1959 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Saint Regis, 1946-1961 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Saint Regis: Minutes, 1952-1959 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Savoy Hilton/Savoy Plaza, 1948-1961 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Savoy Hilton/Savoy Plaza: Functions, Nov 1957 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Savoy Hilton/Savoy Plaza: Functions, Dec 1957 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Savoy Hilton/Savoy Plaza: Functions, Mar 1958 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Savoy Hilton/Savoy Plaza: Functions, May 1958 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Savoy Hilton/Savoy Plaza: Minutes, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Savoy Hilton/Savoy Plaza: Minutes, 1951-1959 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Shelburn, 1948-1954 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Shelburn: Minutes, 1955; 1960 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Shelton, 1948-1956 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Shelton: Minutes, 1951; 1954 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Sheraton East, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Sheraton East: Minutes, 1958-1960 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Sherry Netherland, 1949-1961 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Sherry Netherland: Minutes, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Statler (Pennsylvania), 1948-1950 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Statler: Minutes, 1948-1960 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Statler Hilton, 1936; 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Theresa, 1949-1953 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Theresa: Minutes, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Towers, 1948-1960 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Towers: Minutes, 1951; 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Town House, 1949-1951 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Vanderbilt, 1948-1957 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Vanderbilt: Minutes, 1950-1957 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Victoria, 1949-1952 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Waldorf Astoria, 1948-1953 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Waldorf Astoria, 1954-1961 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Waldorf Astoria: Bass Investigation, 1950-1954 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Waldorf Astoria: Captains, 1948-1951 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Waldorf Astoria: Minutes, 1948-1961 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Warwick, 1948-1958 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Warwick: Minutes, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Westover, 1948-1950 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Woodstock, 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - WIndermere, 1951; 1955 (Box 22, Folder 51)
- Series III: Banquet Department
  - General, 1948-1955 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - General, 1967; 1979-1983 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Anti-Discrimination Cases, 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Applications: Roll Call List, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Applications: Steady Banquet Job, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Applications: Steady Banquet Job, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Applications: Steady Banquet Job, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Applications: Steady Banquet Job, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Attendance Record: Meetings, Jan 1956 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Bartenders' Issues, 1950; 1953; 1961 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement: Hotel Association and Hotel Trades Council, Sep 1949 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Complaint Department, 1944-1947; 1950 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Election Results, 1951; 1954 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee: Grievance and Membership Correspondence, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Grievance and Adjustment Board Decisions, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Hotel Trades Council: General, 1954-1956 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Insurance Claim Information, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Jobs Sent out by Letter, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Jobs Sent out by Letter, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Jobs Sent out by Letter, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Jobs Sent out by Letter, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Kosher Supervisors, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Labor Department: Days Off, 1950-1953 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Lists, 1947-1949 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Minutes: Banquet Department Delegates, 1944-1956 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1948-1955 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Minutes: Membership Meeting, 1950-1955 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Pensions, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Resolutions, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Roll Call, 1948-1961 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Roll Call, 1967-1969; 1982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Rules, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Safety Squad Patrol, Nov 1955 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Sample Ballot, May 1959 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Sick List, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Steady Lists, 1951-1953 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Steady Lists, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Steady Lists, Jan-Aug 1955 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Steady Lists, Sep-Dec 1955 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Steady Lists, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Steady Lists, 1959-1961 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Steady Lists, 1974-1977 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Steady Lists, 1978-1981 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Tips, 1942; 1950 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Wages, 1932-1955 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Wages: Hours and Conditions, 1946-1952 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Series V: Club Department
  - Subseries V:A: General Files
    - General, undated; 1938-1982 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Arbitrations, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Assembly Delegates, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Bargaining, 1958-1974 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Cases, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Check-Off, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Complaints, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Convention, 1953-1954 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Convention, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Convention Delegates, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Convention Reports, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Dues Increase Referendum, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Elections, 1950s-1960s (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Executive Board and Committees, 1950-1951 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Kirkwood, Joseph: Racquet and Tennis Club, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Leaflets, 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Medical Insurance, 1961-1966 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Minutes, 1957-1967 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Pattern Settlements, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Pension Fund, 1952-1957 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Pension Fund, 1958-1967 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Pension Fund, 1976-1980 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Pension Fund, 1985-1988 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Pension Fund: Agreement, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Pension Fund: Regulations, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Pension Fund: Trustees, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Pension Reciprocity, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Racial Discrimination, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Referendum, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Sample Clauses, 1950s-1960s (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Settlements, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Sirch, Richard, 1956-1963 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Training Program, undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Wage Rates, 1953-1956 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Subseries V:B: Clubs
    - Advertising, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Advertising: Contracts, 1963-1970 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Advertising: Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - American Women's Association: Organizing, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Arkwright, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Atrium, 1980-1991 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Bankers, 1964-1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Bankers: Contracts, 1963-1972 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Bankers: Correspondence, 1955; 1960-1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Board Room, 1969-1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Broad Street, 1951-1988 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Broad Street: Contracts, 1959-1970 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Brook, 1957-1965; 1970-1987 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Brook: Contracts, 1956-1972 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Brook: Correspondence, 1956-1985 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Brooklyn, 1954-1970 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Brooklyn: Contracts, 1955-1972 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Brooklyn: Correspondence, 1955-1975 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Building Trades Employers Association, 1952-1958; 1970 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Building Trades Employers Association: Contracts, 1956-1973 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Building Trades Employers Association: Correspondence, 1952-1964 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Century, 1952-1957; 1970-1975; 1991 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Century: Contracts, 1953-1976; 1982 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Century: Correspondence, 1952-1977 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Chemists', 1975-1988 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Chemists': Contracts, 1961-1969 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Chemists': Correspondence, 1963-1985 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Citicorp Center, 1981-1988 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - City Athletic, 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - City Athletic: Contracts, 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - City Athletic: Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - City Midday, 1951-1960; 1970 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - City Midday: Correspondence, 1949-1975 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Cloud, 1947-1970 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Club 101, 1984-1990 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Colony, 1941; 1966-1985 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Colony: Contracts, 1958-1978 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Columbia University, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Columbia University, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Columbia University: Contracts, 1947-1957 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Cornell, 1963-1981 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Cosmopolitan, 1956; 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Cosmopolitan: Contracts, 1955-1975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Cosmopolitan: Correspondence, 1955-1978 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Dartmouth College, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Downtown Association, 1951-1976 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Downtown Association: Contracts, 1953-1976 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Downtown Association: Correspondence, 1951-1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Downtown Athletic, 1951-1957; 1963-1971 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Downtown Athletic: Contracts, 1949-1973 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Drug and Chemical: Correspondence, 1952-1966 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Empire State, 1951-1956; 1970; 1981 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Empire State: Contracts, 1954-1970 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Empire State: Correspondence, 1951-1972 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Engineers, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Fifth Avenue, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Fifth Avenue: Correspondence, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Five Hundred, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Harbor View, 1963-1975 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Harbor View: Arbitration, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Harbor View: Contracts, 1960-1975 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Harbor View: Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Harmonie, 1952-1973 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Harmonie: Contracts, 1953-1965 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Harmonie: Correspondence, 1948-1975 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Harvard, 1948; 1961-1965 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Harvard: Contracts, 1957-1973 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Harvard: Correspondence, 1959-1973 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - India House, 1951-1957 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - India House, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - India House: Contracts, 1949-1975 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - India House: Correspondence, 1948-1974 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Knickerbocker, 1955-1970 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Knickerbocker: Contracts, 1957-1975 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Knickerbocker: Correspondence, 1957-1978 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Lambs, 1972-1978 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Lawyers, 1970; 1974 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Lawyers: Contracts, 1959-1964 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Lawyers: Correspondence, 1960-1971 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Links, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Links: Contracts, 1959-1966 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Links: Correspondence, 1960-1975 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Lotos, 1955-1982 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Lotos: Contracts, 1955-1975 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Lotos: Correspondence, 1955-1978 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Lunch, 1970-1975 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Lunch: Correspondence, 1960-1972 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Merchants, 1962-1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Merchants: Contracts, 1955-1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Merchants: Correspondence, 1955-1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Metropolitan, 1951-1970 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Metropolitan: Contracts, 1954-1970 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Metropolitan: Correspondence, 1954-1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Opera, 1974-1989 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Metropolitan Opera: Contracts, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Metropolitan Opera: Correspondence, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Montauk, 1952-1962 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Montauk, 1972-1988 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Montauk: Contracts, 1951-1969 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Montauk: Correspondence, 1950-1977 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - National Cleaning, 1975-1981 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - National Democratic, 1966-1970 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - New York Athletic, 1941; 1951-1985 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - New York Athletic: Contracts, 1954-1974 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - New York Athletic: Correspondence, 1950-1966 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - New York Athletic: Correspondence, 1967-1977 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - New York Athletic vs. Local 6 et al., 1974 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - New York Produce Exchange, 1950-1970 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - New York Produce Exchange: Contracts, 1954-1967 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - New York Produce Exchange: Correspondence, 1952-1967 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - New York University, undated; 1955-1988 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - New York University: Contracts, 1956-1974 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - New York University: Correspondence, 1956-1972 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - New York Yacht, 1955-1987 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - New York Yacht: Contracts, 1958-1975 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - New York Yacht: Correspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Overseas Press, 1956-1975 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Overseas Press: Contracts, 1958-1975 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Overseas Press: Correspondence, 1956-1973 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Pinnacle, 1955-1985 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Pinnacle: Correspondence, 1957-1972 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Pinnacle: Contracts, 1956-1975 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Players, 1951-1992 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Players: Contracts, 1956-1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Players: Correspondence, 1952-1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Princeton, undated; 1947-1990 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Princeton: Contracts, 1954-1963 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Princeton: Correspondence, 1953-1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Racquet and Tennis, 1955-1995 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Racquet and Tennis: Contracts, 1956-1972 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Racquet and Tennis: Correspondence, 1956-1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Railroad Machinery, 1953-1960 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Railroad Machinery: Correspondence, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Recess, 1952-1983 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Recess: Contracts, 1972-1977 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Recess: Correspondence, 1951-1979 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - River, 1952-1985 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - River: Contracts, 1954-1976 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - River: Correspondence, 1952-1977 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Royal Globe, 1952-1984 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Royal Globe (Royal Insurance): Contracts, 1954-1973 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Royal Globe (Royal Liverpool): Correspondence, 1952-1976 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Seven Arts, 1956-1961 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Sixty East, 1960-1990 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Sixty East: Correspondence, 1959-1975 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Sky, 1953-1988 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Sky: Correspondence, 1964-1976 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Stock Exchange Luncheon, 1951-1964; 1975-1984 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Stock Exchange Luncheon: Contracts, 1961-1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Stock Exchange Luncheon: Correspondence, 1952-1978 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Stork Club, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Town Club: Correspondence, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Trade Center, 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Trader Vic's, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Traffic, 1960-1975 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Traffic: Contracts, 1960-1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Traffic: Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Two Hundred Fifth Avenue, 1983-1990 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Union, undated; 1951-1990 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Union: Contracts, 1955-1966 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Union: Correspondence, 1952-1969 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Union League, undated; 1952 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - University, 1951-1987 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - University: Contracts, 1956-1969 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - University: Correspondence, 1951-1975 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Uptown, 1950-1959 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Wall Street, 1951-1989 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Wall Street: Contracts, 1961-1972 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Wall Street: Correspondence, 1952-1976 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Weavers, 1961-1976 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Whitehall, 1952-1957; 1970 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Whitehall: Contracts, 1959-1973 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Whitehall: Correspondence, 1952-1977 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Williams, 1952-1988 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Williams: Contracts, 1952-1972 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Williams: Correspondence, 1952-1977 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Yacht, 1954-1981 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Yale, undated; 1952-1990 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Yale: Contracts, 1955-1972 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Yale: Correspondence, 1952-1975 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Series VI: Restaurant Division
  - Subseries V:A: General Files
    - Background: General, 1962-1982 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Broadway Joe's Steakhouse, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Business Agents, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Business Agents' Territories, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Business Agents' Territories, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Lists, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Luchow's, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Robsan (Ziegfeld's), 1975 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Sky Chefs, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Squire's Intermission, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Terminations, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Windows on the World, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Subseries V:B: HERE, Local 1 Records
    - Arbitration, Playboy Club, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Bargaining, 1970-1973 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Bylaws, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Delmonico's, 1983-1986 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Education Committee, 1967-1977 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Elections, 1961-1977 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Farm Workers: Minimum Wage, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Jurisdictional Problems, 1969-1973 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Latin Quarter Café Dispute, 1968-1971 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Legislative, 1967-1973 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Local 11 (Chain Restaurant and Luncheonette Union): General, 1960-1972 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Other Locals: Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Restaurant Clean-Up, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Restaurant Contracts: A, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Ba-Be, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Bi-Bu, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Ca-Ce, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Ch, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Cl-Cu, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Restaurant Contracts: D, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Restaurant Contracts: E, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Fa-Fi, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Fo-Fr, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Ga-Ge, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Gi-Gr, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Ha-He, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Hi-Hy, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Restaurant Contracts: I-J, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Restaurant Contracts: K, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Restaurant Contracts: La-Le, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Li-Lo, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Lu, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Ma, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Mc-Me, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Mi-Mu, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Restaurant Contracts: N, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Restaurant Contracts: O, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Pa-Pe, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Pi-Q, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Ra-Re, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Ri-Ru, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Sa-Sc, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Sh-Sm, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Sp-Sw, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Restaurant Contracts: T, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Restaurant Contracts: V, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Restaurant Contracts: W, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Restaurant Contracts: Y-Z, 1950s (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Series VII: Editor's Files.
  - Agreements: Out of State Hotels, 1950-1953 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Bahamas, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Bartenders, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Bickford's, Inc., 1937 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Biographical Information: Various, 1978-1985 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - By-Laws Discussion, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Central Park Zoo Cafeteria, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Childs Restaurant Co.: Clippings, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Civil Rights, 1958-1964 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Consumers Cooperative, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Council Committee News, 1952-1953 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Council History: Correspondence, 1937; 1946 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Council History: Leaflets and Newsletters, undated; 1937; 1940 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Council History: Press Articles and Reports, 1938-1964 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Drakes, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Exchange Buffet, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 16)